{
    "subject": "resource/1040_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Evan_Jackson_Leong",
    "human_readable": "The director of film 1040 is Evan Jackson Leong.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9248228073120117,
            "question": "Is Evan Jackson Leong a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9059327244758606,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Evan Jackson Leong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8950980305671692,
            "question": "Who directed the film 1040?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8745570778846741,
            "question": "Is Evan Jackson Leong a famous director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8100313544273376,
            "question": "Who directed the film with the number 1040 in its title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8004862070083618,
            "question": "Is Evan Jackson Leong involved in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.776992678642273,
            "question": "Can you name a film directed by Evan Jackson Leong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6224704384803772,
            "question": "What is Evan Jackson Leong known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5158742070198059,
            "question": "What film has the number '1040' in its title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5094853639602661,
            "question": "What kind of work does Evan Jackson Leong do?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of film 1040 is Evan Jackson Leong.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7260_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film has the number '1040' in its title?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7260_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Evan Jackson Leong known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7260_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a film directed by Evan Jackson Leong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7260_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7260_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7260_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7260_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7260_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7260_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7260_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7260_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7260_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7260_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7260_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in `54.txt` and `16.txt`, which both confirm that Evan Jackson Leong directed the documentary film \"1040.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}